(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-14T04:45:34.652675",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Around the world
everyone says
that love is just like a dream
feel like I'm melting from the heat
love, it feels so serene
ooh yeah, ooh
just like that you know just how it goes
pineapple
around the world
you already know
You're just so sweet my baby
got me wanting more so tasty, yeah
I don't got no worries, I feel good good good
The warm sun on me, I wanna go and party
Don't let this love end, nah I won't pretend
My best recipe for love is you + me
I wanna try it now
Pineapple
I'm goin' 1 2 – 1 2 3
It tastes so s-s-sweet when you go and kiss me
I'm takin' the perfect picture
You're stuck to me like a sticker
You got that pineapple, pineapple
It tastes so s-s-sweet, go that way
Ayaya ayaya, keep goin', you know me
Ayaya ayaya, pineapple – hey!
I'm with you beating the heat, so sweet it's hypnotizing, got you dancing to my beat
You gon' be my boo! Yeah
Now you see me see me, babe I need it so just gimme gimme, no more hesitation, don't think twice 'cause you're mine
The warm sun on me, I wanna go and party
Don't let this love end, nah I won't pretend
My best recipe for love is you + me
I wanna try it now
Pineapple
I'm goin' 1 2 – 1 2 3
It tastes so s-s-sweet when you go and kiss me
I'm takin' the perfect picture
You're stuck to me like a sticker
You got that pineapple, pineapple
It tastes so s-s-sweet, go that way
Ayaya ayaya, keep goin', you know me
Ayaya ayaya, pineapple!
Pineapple, pineapple, pineapple, pine ya, come on boy, let's go!
Pineapple, pineapple, pineapple, pine ya, come on baby, do it over over
Hold my hand and let's fly and let's take it to the sky!
Pineapple
I'm goin' 1 2 – 1 2 3
It tastes so s-s-sweet when you go and kiss me
I'm takin' the perfect picture
You're stuck to me like a sticker
You got that pineapple, pineapple
It tastes so s-s-sweet, go that way
Ayaya ayaya, keep goin', you know me
Ayaya ayaya, pineapple!
Waking up in shades of blue
I don't know where I am or how I got to you
Try to reach out, but I can't move
I'm like a broken instrument, so out of tune
Why won't they listen to me anyway?
I wanna be and I'm not gonna say I'm sorry, just so you'll let me stay, no
Whatever you think of me, leave it alone
I don't wanna live in the shade of her throne
Pieces of a melody playing in my head
fragments of a past that it won't let me forget
Someone that I used to be hanging on a thread
a blurry silhouette, I wonder... when you look at me, who do you remember?
Broken memories, time we spent together
Tell me honestly, do you recognize my voice, voice?
Thin air, so hard to breathe, the wall that I'm facing is just too cold and too lonely
Wish that I still can feel, still can feel the things that back then I used to feel
All I ever wanted is to be accepted by you
Wish that you and I still laugh and say that someday we will
Why won't you listen to me anyway?
I'm gonna be and I'm not gonna say I'm sorry
just to save face
Whatever you think of me, leave it alone
I don't wanna live in the shade of her throne
Pieces of a melody playing in my head
fragments of a past that it won't let me forget
Someone that I used to be hanging on a thread
a blurry silhouette, I wonder... when you look at me, who do you remember?
hanging on the thread of blurry silhouette
I wonder...
When you look at me, who do you remember?
Broken memories, time we spent together
Tell me honestly, do you recognize my voice? Voice
It looks so off to me, the picture you paint of us
I don't need to remember, let me be, take me just as I am, yeah
Everything disappears, I shout to heavens above
Let me be, take me just as I am, yeah
Pieces of a melody playing in my head, fragments of a past that it won't let me forget
Someone that I used to be
Hanging on the thread of blurry silhouette
I wonder...
When you look at me, who do you remember?
Broken memories, time we spent together
Tell me honestly, do you think that I could ever find a voice to call my own?
Voice, voice
好きなんの? どころ? Go, go! ワイアーいいどわけっま?
What do you like? Go, go! Why is it okay? Yes, mama!
誰も彼もがセイボン・ダ・メ・メ!
Everyone is safe and sound, no, no!
どこに投げてるのの?
Where are you throwing it?
ベッドの誘いあいっこ
Inviting each other to bed, mutual icons!
あなごあ、いってる? レートー男々々!
Are you saying that? Frozen men, men, men!
恋ぐらいしちゃってそうぜん
Falling in love makes it a sensation!
好き好き好き! 僕のバレンタイン!
Suki, suki, suki! My Valentine!
好き好き好き! スロボ無限大!
Suki, suki, suki! Robot infinity!
好き好き好き! スロボわかるわ!
Suki, suki, suki! I understand the robot!
好き好き好き! スロボだったまんま!
Suki, suki, suki! Remaining just like a robot!
シャバダラララララ、ロボロボ!
Shabada lalalalala, robo robo!
これであの娘と友情?
Is this friendship with that girl?
のねじゃカレシとフェイルアウト!
Or failing out with a boyfriend?
なんてこうじゃの永久だめだめ!
Why is it forever no, no?
レッスン作っても、あたたかみも承知してヘッヘラ!
Even if we make lessons, knowing the warmth, hehela!
恋のゆくえはありがたかっただけ
The destination of love was just appreciated!
いつまでも子供じゃないのね!
We're not kids anymore, you know!
好き好き好き! スロボだったまい!
Suki, suki, suki! I was a robot!
好き好き好き! スロボはコショウね!
Suki, suki, suki! The robot has pepper!
好き好き好き! スロボはひとりじゃ!
Suki, suki, suki! The robot is alone!
好き好き好き! スロボ誰もできません!
Suki, suki, suki! No one can do it!
好き好き好き! スロボください!
Suki, suki, suki! Please give me a robot!
好き好き好き! スロボはコショウね!
Suki, suki, suki! The robot has pepper!
好き好き好き! スロボはひとりじゃ!
Suki, suki, suki! The robot is alone!
すごい あのこ は go girl
That awesome girl's a go girl
やばい あいつ は yes man
That cool guy's a yes man
誰も 彼 も が 平凡？
He and everybody else, all ordinary?
ダメダメ
No, that won't do!
何処 に 投げ て ん の！？ ノーコン
Where you throw in ' that?! No control
デート の 誘い アイコン
You asking me out on a date ── eye contact
穴 が 開い てる レンコン
An open hole ── some lotus root
などなど
Etc. etc.
恋 ぐらい 知っ て て 当然
I at least know what love's all about ── that should be obvious
好き 好きっす キス を ください
I like you like you won't you please kiss me?
好き 好きっす キス を 無限大
I like you like you won't you kiss me infinitely?
好き 好きっす キス は わかる わ
I like you like you I know what kisses are
好き 好きっす ロボット だって
I like you like you even though I'm a robot
シャバラ ラン ラン ラン ラン ラン ラーラ
Shabala lan lan lan lan, la la
ロボロボ
Robo robo
せーの
One, two
でも そんなんじゃ だーめ
It's so hard to say it
もう そんなんじゃ ほーら
But darling let's face it
心は進化するよ もーっと もーっと
These feelings revealing cannot be ignored
言葉にすれば 消えちゃう関係なら
If you're scared that you'll say something you'll regret, well
言葉を消せばいいやって 思ってた 恐れてた
Love is something that's best when quiet
だけど あれ? なんか 違うかも
Just shut up! Wait a second, that ain't right
千里の道も一歩から
Every journey's gotta start with a step
石のように固い そんな意志で
So go on out there and give it your best
塵も積もればやまとなでしこ?
I'm takin' a chance cuz i like you a lot
しーぬきで いや しにぬきで
So i'll give it a shot, give it all that i got
ふわふわり ふわふわる
La de da de da / La de da de de
あなたが 名前を呼ぶ それだけで宙へ浮かぶ
Suddenly you call my name / And i lose my brain / And i float up to the moon
ふわふわる ふわふわり
La de da de de / La de da de da
あなたが笑っている それだけで笑顔になる
When you laugh it makes me smile / And i love your style / So i wrote a song to this tune
神様 ありがとう
Thank you stars for giving to me
運命のいたずでも
The greatest gift that's still yet to be
めぐり逢えたことが 幸せなの
I don't mind if fate's playing games / I'm happy all the same
でも そんなんじゃ だーめ
It's so hard to say it
もう そんなんじゃ ほーら
But darling let's face it
心は進化するよ もーっと もーっと
These feelings revealing cannot be ignored
そう そんなんじゃ やだー
So i'll work on this letter
ねぇ そんなんじゃ まーだ
'Til our timing gets better
私のこと見ててね ざーっと ざーっと
Sincerely, yours truly / And forevermore
恋愛サーキュレーション 私の中のあなたほど あなたの中の私の存在は まだまだ大きくないこともわかっているけれど
Look i know it's a lot and it's unrefined, but / I can't seem to get you off of my mind / You feel the same? I'll take your name! / Maybe not. I guess that's okay
今この同じ 瞬間 共有してる実感
Oh can't you see / Love me / We're meant to be / Love me / 'Cause i won't stop till you look my way
塵も積もればやまとなでしこ 略してちりつもやまとなでしこ
Come what may! Do whatever it takes / My oh me oh my / My oh my oh me
くらくらり くらくやる
Suddenly i catch your eye / Then i'm petrified / And i melt into my shoes
あなたを見上げたら それだけで眩しすぎて
My oh my oh me / My oh me oh my
くらくやる くらくらり
Every day is like a dream / A real fantasy / Whenever i'm with you
あなたを思ってて それだけで飛びてしまう
Thank you stars for giving to me / The greatest gift that's still yet to be / I don't mind if fate's playing games / I'm happy all the same
神様 ありがとう 運命のいたずでも めぐり逢えたことが しあわせなの
Lonely hearts from every nation / Come on do the circulation / It's a dance of admiration / Let's all do the circulation
恋する季節は欲張りサーキュレーション
Move with your imagination / Come on do the circulation / Join the endless flagellation / Let's all do the circulation
恋する気持ちは欲張りサーキュレーション
La de da de da / La de da de de / Suddenly you call my name / And i lose my brain / And i float up to the moon
恋する瞳は欲張りサーキュレーション
La de da de de / La de da de da / When you laugh it makes me smile / And i love your style / So i wrote a song to this tune
恋する乙女は欲張りサーキュレーション
Thank you stars for giving to me / The greatest gift that's still yet to be / I don't mind if fate's playing games / I'm happy all the same
ふわふわり ふわふわる あなたが名前を呼ぶ それだけで宙へ浮かぶ
It's so hard to say it / But darling let's face it / These feelings revealing / Cannot be ignored
ふわふわる ふわふわり あなたが笑っている それだけで笑顔になる
So i'll work on this letter / 'Til our timing gets better / Sincerely, yours truly / And forevermore
神様 ありがとう 運命のいたずでも めぐり逢えたことが しあわせなの
Thank you stars for giving to me / The greatest gift that's still yet to be / I don't mind if fate's playing games / I'm happy all the same
でも そんなんじゃ だーめ もう そんなんじゃ ほーら
It's so hard to say it / But darling let's face it
心は進化するよ もーっと もーっと
These feelings revealing cannot be ignored
そう そんなんじゃ やだー ねぇ そんなんじゃ まーだ
So i'll work on this letter / 'Til our timing gets better
私のこと見ててね ざーっと ざーっと
Sincerely, yours truly / And forevermore
きききはろー！
Ki-Ki-Ki-Hello!
アキ先輩に挨拶して！
Say hello to Aki-senpai!
アロハ！アキロゼんだよー！
Aloha! It's Aki Rosenthal!
一緒に恋愛サーキュレーションしよう！
Let's do Renai Circulation together!
でもその前に、まつり先輩と踊るんでしょ？
But before that, we dance with Matsuri-senpai, right?
だからまつり先輩を呼ぼう！
So let's bring in Matsuri-senpai!
ちょっと、そこが違うけどね！
Wait, the vibe is a bit different though!
かわいい！かわいい！ちっちゃい！
So cute! So small! Thank you!
アキロゼは？アキロゼは？そんなに小さくないけど！
What about Aki? Not that small though!
お姉さん組だね！
We're the big sister group!
質問したい！
I want to ask a question!
お二人は今年一番嬉しかったこと、what was the thing you were most happy about this year?
What was the thing you were most happy about this year?
アキロゼは大好きなクレープ屋さんコラボがいっぱいできたし
Aki got to do lots of collabs with her favorite crêpe shop,
案件も来たこと！
and got sponsored offers too!
クレープうまいし、美味しい！
Crêpes are delicious!
最高最高！二人も来てくれたしね！
Awesome! And you two came too!
またこうしてそうしてください！もちろん！お腹すいた！
Let's do it again! Of course! I'm hungry!
まつりはやっぱり、あの、リスナーさんと楽しい時間を過ごせたことかな？
For Matsuri, it was spending fun time with the listeners this year!
なんでやねん！
Why are you hitting me?!
Her favorite thing was just being with the viewers and hers was being a crepemaker which was really good, yeah.
Her favorite thing was being with viewers, and hers was being a crêpe maker.
私はいろは様のテーマ曲に参加したことと、やっと3Dをお披露目できたこと！
For me, participating in Iroha-sama's theme song and finally doing my 3D reveal!
It's almost 2024. もうすぐ2024年！
It's almost 2024!
ということは、来年、私とやりたいこと、what are you gonna do next year?
What do you want to do next year?
せっかく3人いますからアキロゼの家に行ってご飯食べたい！
Since there are three of us, let's go to Aki's house!
アキロゼの家に行ってご飯食べたい！
Let's go to Aki-senpai's house and eat!
ダンスできるから、ね、ダンスも！
Since we can dance, let's do a dance collab too!
普通に、もっと遊びたい！遊ぼう！ゲームもしたい！
I just want to play more! Let's play! Play games!
英語も教えたほうが
And teach English!
英語メンバーがいっぱいいますから、私はドイツ語を教えてあげる！
There are plenty of English members, so I'll teach German!
グーテンモルゲンってドイツ語？
Guten Morgen in German?
そうそうそう！
That's right!
So maybe we'll you know, we'll get some cooking collabs next year, maybe some dancing, and maybe I'll teach them German, who knows?
So maybe we'll get some cooking collabs next year, some dancing, and maybe I'll teach them German, who knows!
バイバイ！まったねー！ありがとう！
Bye-bye! See you later! Thank you so much!
はじめようぜ
Let's begin!
ぶつかわせ
Clash together!
夢にまでね
Even in our dreams,
上がってこぜ
let's rise up!
雑草を見たいな
Like weeds,
俺たちの生きざまを
living our lives stubbornly,
笑いたい奴らがいたら笑えばいい
laugh if they want to laugh at us.
同じことなんかしたくない
I don't want to do the exact same thing as others.
人と同じである意味信じない
I don't believe in the meaning of being just like everyone else.
だって命が違うのに
After all, each life is different.
何度でも 生まれてやるんだ
No matter how many times, I will be born again!
何度でも かっこつけたままがいいじゃん
No matter how many times, it's fine to stay looking cool!
泥だらけでも 泥しゃぶ泥泥浴びり
Muddy or drenched in mud,
雨でも 涙の夜でも
rain or nights of tears,
倒れたって起き上がれる
even if I fall, I can get back up!
生まれて 生まれて 生まれて
Born, born, born,
もっと強くなるんだ
I will become even stronger!
嫌々ヘラ 甘えてんじゃねえ
Don't act all spoiled and whiny!
はじめようぜ
Let's begin!
ぶつかわせ
Clash together!
夢にまでね
Even in our dreams,
名前も持たない
Having no name,
道端の草みたいに
like grass by the roadside,
誰にも知られて
known by no one,
いない気分はどうだい？
how does that feel?
言い訳してる暇はない
There's no time to make excuses,
落ち込んでるそんな場合じゃない
no time to be feeling down.
そうさ時代は変わるよ
That's right, the times are changing.
生きてるだけで奇跡でさ
Just being alive is a miracle,
素敵でさ、俺たち
so wonderful, all of us.
ボロボロになったっていいじゃん
It's okay if we get tattered and torn,
ゴールなんて馬鹿々々しい
a goal is so foolish.
石ころ道でも線路の脇でも歩道橋の走っても
On stony paths, railway sides, or overpasses,
根っことやればいい
just take root and do it.
蹴られて蹴られて蹴られて何か見つけ出すんだ
Kick, kick, kicked around, find something out.
You can do it 諦めないで
You can do it, don't give up!
夢見て 夢見て 笑って 笑って
Dreaming, dreaming, laughing, laughing,
悩んで 悩んで 涙流してもいいんだ
worrying, worrying, it's okay to shed tears.
夢中で 夢中で 不安で 不安で
Lost in dreams, lost in dreams, feeling uneasy, uneasy,
叫んで 叫んで 求め続けてやろうぜ
screaming, screaming, let's keep searching for it.
カンカン照りでも 土砂降り雨でも
In the blazing sun or downpouring rain,
雪でも 倒れたって起き上がれる
on snowy nights, even if you fall, you can get back up.
踏まれて 踏まれて 踏まれて もっと強くなるんだ
Trampled, trampled, trampled, becoming even stronger.
If your head's up 諦めないで
If your head's up, don't give up!
始めようぜ ハイハイハイ
Let's get started! (Hai, hai, hai!)
ぶつかろうぜ ハイハイハイ
Let's clash head-on! (Hai, hai, hai!)
夢見とけよ ハイハイハイ
Keep dreaming! (Hai, hai, hai!)
上がってこうぜ ピース！
Let's rise up, peace!
this fever’s got no fall
This fever's got no fall
temperatures crazy off the wall
get ready like stop , drop , roll
Get ready like stop, drop, roll
not gonna break a sweat at all
sparks light that candle fire
the phoenix rises higher
frigid , frozen , no limits
Frigid, frozen, no limits
deadly co - o - old
Deadly co-o-old
ten below - oh - oh
Ten below-oh-oh
支配したいよ 君の心を
I want to rule over your heart.
「いい子？」 「僕の？」
"A good boy?" "Mine?"
no more
fire it up , fire it up now hot passion , never back down
Fire it up, fire it up now / Hot passion, never back down
freeze you out , freeze you out now not about to bend to you
Freeze you out, freeze you out now / Not about to bend to you
fire and ice , death and life , now high pressure , turn it up loud
Fire and ice, death and life, now / High pressure, turn it up loud
fire and ice , fire and ice , now this world is all smoke and mirrors
Fire and ice, fire and ice, now / This world's all smoke and mirrors
na - na - na - na - na 君の想う価値
Na-na-na-na-na, what you think it's worth
na - na - na - na - na 超えて超えて
Na-na-na-na-na, go beyond, go beyond
na - na - na - na - na じっと息を呑んで
Na-na-na-na-na, holding your breath
na - na - na - na - na 染めて染めて
Na-na-na-na-na, dye it, dye it
blazing , unchanging no strange thing about this heat , witness me
Blazing, unchanging, no strange thing about this heat, witness me
hit this beat , rinse repeat these feelings got me freezing up
Hit this beat, rinse repeat, these feelings got me freezing up
中毒性の愛は 身体中、今かけ巡らせば
If this addictive love courses through my body right now
can’t control , overflow
Can't control, overflow
つかまえたいの君の心を
I want to catch your heart.
「でもね？」 「だてに？」
"But you know?" "For nothing?"
no more
fire it up , fire it up now hot passion , never back down
Fire it up, fire it up now / Hot passion, never back down
freeze you out , freeze you out now not about to bend to you
Freeze you out, freeze you out now / Not about to bend to you
fire and ice , death and life , now high pressure , turn it up loud
Fire and ice, death and life, now / High pressure, turn it up loud
fire and ice , fire and ice , now this world is all smoke and mirrors
Fire and ice, fire and ice, now / This world's all smoke and mirrors
na - na - na - na - na うるさいその口
Na-na-na-na-na, shut that noisy mouth
na - na - na - na - na 閉じて閉じて
Na-na-na-na-na, close it, close it
na - na - na - na - na 有毒性の「I」を
Na-na-na-na-na, pour in toxic "I"
na - na - na - na - na 込め込め
Na-na-na-na-na, pack it in, pack it in
we’re caught up in the eye of a storm of flame
We're caught up in the eye of a storm of flame
it’s not complicated , but a nuanced game
It's not complicated, but a nuanced game
a past you once gave me something i can’t shake
A past you once gave me something I can't shake
the chance knowing somebody who had moves to make
so whatcha waiting for ? you gotta burn it up
So whatcha waiting for? You gotta burn it up
'cause when it rains it pours , you gotta earn the love
'Cause when it rains it pours, you gotta earn the love
i’m never given in , they’ll never get enough
I'm never giving in, they'll never get enough
'cause you and i always rise above , you got it ?
'Cause you and I always rise above, you got it?
fire it up , fire it up now hot passion , never back down
Fire it up, fire it up now / Hot passion, never back down
freeze you out , freeze you out now not about to bend to you
Freeze you out, freeze you out now / Not about to bend to you
fire and ice , death and life , now high pressure , turn it up loud
Fire and ice, death and life, now / High pressure, turn it up loud
fire and ice , fire and ice , now this world is all smoke and mirrors
Fire and ice, fire and ice, now / This world's all smoke and mirrors
na - na - na - na - na 君の想う価値
Na-na-na-na-na, what you think it's worth
na - na - na - na - na 超えて超えて
Na-na-na-na-na, go beyond, go beyond
na - na - na - na - na じっと息を呑んで
Na-na-na-na-na, holding your breath
na - na - na - na - na 染めて染めて
Na-na-na-na-na, dye it, dye it
欲せよその愛は
Desire that love
込めて込めて
Pour it in, pour it in
we caught up in the eye of a storm of flame
it’s not complicated , but a nuanced game
It's not complicated, but a nuanced game
a past you once gave me something i can’t shake
A past you once gave me something I can't shake
the chance knowing somebody who had moves to make
so whatcha waiting for ? you gotta burn it up
So whatcha waiting for? You gotta burn it up
'cause when it rains it pours , you gotta earn the love
'Cause when it rains it pours, you gotta earn the love
This fever's got no fall
Temperature's crazy off the wall
Get ready like stop, drop, roll
Not gonna break a sweat at all
Sparks light that candle fire
The phoenix rises higher
Frigid, frozen, no limits
Deadly cold, ten below
支配したいのさ 君の心を
I just wanna rule your heart
「 いい子 ? 」 「 僕 の ? 」
"Good girl?" "Mine?"
no more!
fire it up, fire it up now
hot passion, never back down
freeze you out, freeze you out now
not about to bend to you
fire and ice, death and life, now
high pressure, turn it up loud
fire and ice, fire and ice, now
this world's all smoke and mirrors
na-na-na-na-na
君 の 想う 価値観
Whatever you think you're worth
超 えて 超 えて
Above and beyond
じ っ と 息 を 呑 ん で
While holding your breath
染 め て 染 め て
Dye it over and over
Thank you everybody!
Woo!
Hi, hi, hi, hi!
Takanashi Kiara, Mori Calliope!
Thank you so much, everybody!
How was it? How was it?
Did you like it?
I hope so.
We worked very hard on that.
That's our brand new song!
A brand new song, but we wanted to talk more about it.
And we want to get down closer to you guys so you can hear us, right?
That's right.
Let's get closer here. Hello!
We're going to jump, right?
That's right. Wait, really?
Are you ready to jump? It's pretty far!
Are you sure?
Kiara, are you okay?
Die, are you sure?
You're high! Falling down!
Swagger, hey!
Easy, so easy.
Such a high jump there.
Up there.
I can't believe we didn't die.
Must be because of me.
That's crazy!
Oh, man.
Nice!
You guys hear us and see us better now?
Hello, hello!
Hi!
Loud and clear, Takamori!
Takamori, Takamori!
Welcome, welcome, welcome!
I hope you guys enjoyed the song.
Ooh, I think it was hype.
Mmm, I think so. It's a banger!
So, now we can talk about the song...
and I think you know the most details about it, so give me the deets.
Well, this song has been in the works for about two years.
A long time. Hey!
Everyone's really busy all the time, right?
But, you know what, it was finally time to finish it.
Yeah, 'cause I said, Calli, I'm doing this birthday live thing, do you maybe want to release it in time for that? And that kind of got us finally rolling, right?
Finally got the ball rolling, got it moving...
And um, it's called "Fire N Ice," which...
Are you fire?
No.
Am I fire?
Fire!
Is that a real question? She's messing with me. She knows I'm fire!
I'm the fire!
Yeah, you're the ice!
Oh, my god.
This song is about us, and how we're very different, but when we get together, we make magic happen. Bangers, etc.
Yeah, that that was the basic idea. And it's produced by TeddyLoid who always makes bangers.
TeddyLoid always makes bangers!
Once a moss.
So, thank you.
Arigato gozaimasu.
And um, lyrics by both myself and TeddyLoid.
So, I hope you guys enjoy it. The music video is on my channel. It came out like a couple days ago, so go check it.
It's so cool!
Yeah. And the music video is really neat.
It's by Kannauru.
Kannauru, who also always only makes bangers. So, be sure you check it.
Yeah. Should we show...
Should we show...
Should we show the jacket?
The jacket?
Oh, yeah, the jacket!
Yeah, the jacket!
Check it out! You guys have jackets?
We're selling jackets?
Oh, my god!
She's messing with me again!
Oh, sorry, it's art.
Check it out, chat.
There it is!
We're a meme right now.
Yeah, we are.
Ora, jia jia!
Oh, it's super nice!
Yeah, of course. Who drew the jacket?
It was by Gumshrew.
Yeah! Thank you so much, Gumshrew!
Wow, wow. Comes handy down.
Oh, okay. We're running out of time, but I also want to say like, we came from, you know, small Takamori doing like little cover like Wawa World...
and now we have an original song.
Thank you, Calli, for organizing it.
Yeah, no problem.
Thank you, Shion. And yeah, look at us being cute.
Wow. Last, but not least, we look nice together.
Pose!
Thank you! That was so embarrassing!
Thank you for supporting Takamori! I guess we look cute, maybe.
Thanks for having me. Thank you for coming and dancing with me, it was so fun!
Thank you! I'm getting kicked out again. Yes, sorry, I figured as much.
Bye-bye! See you soon.
Oh well, good luck, and enjoy, everybody! Bye-bye! Peace!
And with that, I still have a lot more songs for you guys. Madamada ikimasu yo! You're going to like this next song, I think. I'm pretty sure. Enjoy.
Lonely ロリロリ神、降臨
Lonely loli-loli god, descends,
鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
Ringing the bell, right this way,
これは救済のレクイエム せーのっ
This is the requiem of salvation. Ready, set—
触ったら逮捕!
You're touched, you're arrested!
極chu♡de!点呼!
Extreme roll call with a kiss!
いちにーさんしー? (ごめんなさい)
One, two, three, four? (So sorry!)
ハア? (ﾟДﾟ)ごめんなさいが、聞こえーない (え~!)
Huh? I can't hear your apology (Eh?!)
粛聖!! ロリ神レクイエム☆
Shukusei!! Loli-gami Requiem☆
将来はお前なんかに好かれたくない
In the future, I don't want to be liked by someone like you
お前なんかには使えるたくない
I wouldn't use someone like you.
泥水で口を洗え 法廷で会おうね
Wash your mouth out with mud, let's meet in court, okay?
さあ おまわりさん 連れて行って
Come on, officer, take them away,
妄想しか取り柄のない かわいそうな人
pitiful people whose only trait is delusion.
その姿貌に見せられますか?
Can you show me that appearance?
わぁ、ありがとう、お疲れ様です
Wow, thank you, great work!
lonely ロリロリ神、降臨 マジヤバ奴等に用心
Lonely loli-loli god descending, watch out for dangerous folks.
まともじゃないなら 早く消えてください
If you're not normal, hurry up and disappear.
lonely ロリロリ神、降臨 鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
Lonely loli-loli god descending, ringing the bell just like this,
とても優しくて 素敵なお兄ちゃん
such a kind and wonderful big brother,
楽園でホラ ねんねしな
now go to sleep in paradise, see?
ほら。世の中には、こんなに気持ち悪い人たちが
Look, in this world, there are so many
蔓延しているんですっ! みーんな、晒し上げますよ。
creepy people spreading everywhere! I'll expose you all.
触ったら逮捕!極chu de!点呼!
Touch me and you're arrested! Ultimate chu! Roll call!
いちにーさんしー? ごめんなさい
One, two, three, four? Sorry!
ハー? ごめんなさいが、聞こえーない
Huh? I can't hear your apology!
はぁーい、獄中にいるみなしゅーぁーん
Hiii, everyone in the slammer!
刑務所ファミリーミーティングの時間でぇーす
It's prison family meeting time!
その、腐りきった耳をゴリゴリかっぽじって
Dig out those rotten ears of yours
よーく聞いてくださいね
and listen closely, okay?
ざーこ キモキモ
Trash, gross!
うるさい 黙ってもらって
Annoying, can you shut up?
嫌いです かわいそ
I hate you, pathetic!
どうしようもない お兄ちゃんお姉ちゃん
Hopeless big brothers and big sisters,
もう希望なんてない
there's no hope left.
可愛いお兄ちゃんお姉ちゃん
Cute big brothers and big sisters,
もう希望なんてない
there's no hope left.
顔面消毒リスキバンス
Facial disinfection riskibounce,
こういうセーカイ カツドウ
this kind of correct activity,
翫聖ロリ神のトイエモウ
the requiem of the sacred loli god!
ハイ、俗世居る皆さん キモキモファミリーミーティングの時間です
Hey, everyone in the mortal world, it's creepy family meeting time!
ああ、この夜の肉蛆を 集めて描いてみるよ
Ah, gathering and drawing the flesh maggots of this night...
真っ白なキャンバスが 汚れて怠けている
A pure white canvas is soiled and lazy.
ロリ振り向いた少女は そっと手を掴む
The loli turning around gently grabs my hand,
楽園などないから
because there is no paradise.
大きな友達のみんなね
Hey, all you big kids,
お前らが落ち込んでいる今日もには どんな意味があるの?
what meaning is there in your depressed days?
ねぇ、教えてよ
Hey, tell me!
lonely ロリロリ神、降臨
Lonely loli-loli god descending,
さようなら 笑顔でタイバイ
goodbye, smiling big bye-bye!
日々を踊ろう どうぞ その手で押してあげる
Dance through the days, go on, I'll push you with that hand.
lonely ロリロリ神、降臨
Lonely loli-loli god descending,
楽園でホラ ねんねしな
now go to sleep in paradise, see?
それは旧時代の
That is from an old era,
レクイエム
a requiem!
ざーこ、あそぼ キモキモ、わかる
Trash, let's play; gross, I understand.
うるさい、黙って かわいそう、たすけて
Annoying, shut up; pathetic, save me.
ざーこ、わろ、みっともな 冗談じゃない
Trash, lol, pathetic—no joke!
本当に気持ち悪い
Truly disgusting.
passing by familiar roads, i couldn't find the reason why
who i am you couldn't know
stuck in the ruins, my disillusion
in between a dual reality
my own desire keeps me to you, ooh
Passing by familiar roads
Moving faster than the light can
I'm in the absence, alone looking back
Did I lose my way
I can't see the day
When I can reach you again
Then can I let go?
I can hear your voice
Leading me through the void
Fade away to the grey
Eternally I'm walking by the lives that flash before my eyes
Alone, the silence deafening, still I'm reaching out to you
Connections sacrificed, the lie I tell myself so I'll survive
One day, eventually the light, it will lead me back, do you see me?
Da da d- da d- da da da ooh (wanderer)
Da da da da da da da, ooh (Wanderer)
Da da d- da d- da da da I am the wanderer
Da da da da da da da, I am the wanderer
Da da d- da d- da da da ooh (wanderer)
Da da da da da da da, ooh (Wanderer)
Da da d- da d- da da da I am the wanderer
Da da da da da da da, I am the wanderer
Faith is gone, the well is dry
No more believing, just deceiving
Feel the daylight on the edge but
I can't feel the heat, fall back I'm too deep
Did I lose my way
I can't see the day
When I can reach you again
Then can I let go?
I can hear your voice
Leading me through the void
Fade away to the grey
Eternally I'm walking by the lives that flash before my eyes
Alone, the silence deafening, still I'm reaching out to you
Connections sacrificed, the lie I tell myself so I'll survive
One day, eventually the light, it will lead me back, do you see me?
Da da d- da d- da da da ooh (wanderer)
Da da da da da da da, ooh (Wanderer)
Da da d- da d- da da da I am the wanderer
Da da da da da da da, I am the wanderer
Da da d- da d- da da da ooh (wanderer)
Da da da da da da da, ooh (Wanderer)
Da da d- da d- da da da I am the wanderer
Da da da da da da da, I am the wanderer
Woo! That was...
TGW, The Great Wanderer!
TGWW, The Great Wanderer!
You were all waiting for that one, weren't you? Me too, me too!
Ah, I feel like the vibe was definitely there. Did you feel it?
The Great Wanderer on my album POV, Point of View right now.
So if you want to hear more of that... and if that was the first time you heard it, then what are you doing? Go listen to my album, please!
Yeah, I really like the choreography, so I hope I can dance it again sometime soon.
And actually, I don't know if you know it yet, but right after this—because this is, you know, as you can see, already ending soon...
もうすぐ終わるんですけど
It's ending soon, but...
実はこの後メンバーがあります! There is a members-only part following right after this!
Actually, there's a members-only part right after this!
So, please check it out. It's the first time I get to do something like that, so it's really exciting for me.
My members, I hope you will enjoy what I have prepared for you, just a little bit, you know, just a little bit extra.
Yeah, and besides that, of course, I just mentioned that I want to, you know, talk about my album because originally I wanted to do this live during the time when the album was released...
Yeah, and besides that, of course, I just mentioned that I want to talk about my album because originally I wanted to do this live when the album was released...
didn't quite work out, so let me just say it now, guys!
I want to say, everybody, 2023 was a blast.
Thank you for supporting me, thank you for supporting Hololive English and Hololive as a whole,
and me as a musician, of course, this year was all about that, me creating my album, and, yeah, more musical activity.
So let's see where a new year, the new year 2024 will lead us to, hopefully more music, and you guys are going to join me, right?
Mmm!
二千二十三年も終わりなので、今年ありがとうございましたというのもね、言いたかったです。ありがとうございます、皆さん。
Since 2023 is coming to an end, I wanted to say thank you so much for this year. Thank you, everyone.
And the last song, next song is the last song, is also from my album. 次の曲が最後の曲なんですけど、そちらも私のアルバムの曲であって、
The next song is the last song, and it's also a song from my album,
it actually didn't get a 3D MV, so I want you guys to look closely at the performance and at the choreography, okay?
All right. Then please listen to Sleep Talking.
It's been a long day,
Will you call me?
You got me sleep talking,
Sleep talking,
Talk to me boy,
I'm up late already, hit midnight,
Convince myself I'm doing alright, but you know,
Taking one step, taking one back,
When you text me saying no way, no fair,
No fair, no fair, your eyes they telling me
Come here now, I can't wait,
Your body got me talking, breathless you got me wanting,
Oh, baby, don't you know?
Got me, I'm hooked, psycho,
I'm breathing you in, I just can't forget, boy you got me stressed, I'm just wanting it,
Oh, baby, that's what you do,
You got me sleep talking in my dreams,
I'm sleep talking, all these nights it's you,
No more hiding it, nah nah,
Caught up in your orbit,
Sleep talking in my dreams,
I'm sleep talking, all these nights it's you,
Way you gettin' me sleep sleep talking all day,
Hey mista, you got me all day I'm sleep day,
In my dreams I just hear your voice, I ain't got a choice,
Yeah, just like that, baby, you might never know, hey don't you leave me alone,
I'm waiting, head on the phone, so baby, just go and make the call and I'll know
If you really all in it, give it to me now boy,
Your body got me talking, breathless you got me wanting,
Oh, baby, don't you know?
Got me, I'm hooked, psycho,
I'm breathing you in, I just can't forget, boy you got me stressed, I'm just wanting it,
Oh, baby, that's what you do,
You got me sleep talking in my dreams,
I'm sleep talking, all these nights it's you,
No more hiding it, nah nah,
Caught up in your orbit,
Sleep talking in my dreams,
I'm sleep talking, all these nights it's you,
Way you gettin' me sleep sleep talking all day,
You got me sleep talking in the night yeah,
Sleep talking, oh, that's right yeah,
Bambela, bamba, bambello,
You got me feelin' so right,
You got me sleep talking in the night yeah,
Sleep talking, oh, that's right yeah,
Bambela, bamba, bambello, you gon' make me sleep talk everyday,
Hello? Baby, who are you talkin' to? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
If you want it, baby, you know just what you gotta do, you know you want it,
Just one look, done so don't pretend,
Hello?
Baby, who are you talkin' to?
Ooh, it's the moment I can't escape,
I'm breathless, I, I can't deny,
Ooh, it's you who made me this way, ahh,
You got me sleep talking in my dreams,
I'm sleep talking, all these nights it's you,
No more hiding it, nah nah,
Caught up in your orbit,
Sleep talking in my dreams,
I'm sleep talking, all these nights it's you,
Way you gettin' me sleep sleep talking all day,
You got me sleep talking in the night yeah,
Sleep talking, oh, that's right yeah,
Bambela, bamba, bambello,
You got me feelin' so right,
You got me sleep talking in the night yeah,
Sleep talking, oh, that's right yeah,
Bambela, bamba, bambello, you got me feeling so right,
Sleep talking, oh, that's right yeah, you gon' make me sleep talk everyday.
that love is just like a dream,
feel like I'm melting from the heat,
1回最初のほう流してほしい
Please play the beginning part once.
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Beat, beat
Zumida
船長！
Senchou!
またねー
See you later!
Pineapple!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
お疲れ様！ありがとー！
Good job! Thank you!
いい、いい、いい
Good, good, good
顔でっか
Your head is huge!
Oh yeah
たーだー
Tada!
Around the world everyone says
That love is just like a dream
Feel like I'm melting from the heat
Love, it feels so serene
Ooh just like that you know just how it goes
Don't ever stop boy you already know
You're just so sweet my baby
Got me wanting more so tasty, yeah
I don't got no worries, I feel good good good
The warm sun on me, I just wanna go and party
Don't let this love end, nah I won't pretend
Pineapple!
Wake up, get right out of bed